{
    "subject": "resource/Gina_Torres",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/New_York",
    "human_readable": "Gina Torres was born in New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9539656043052673,
            "question": "Gina Torres was born in which American city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9374678134918213,
            "question": "Is Gina Torres originally from New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.918318510055542,
            "question": "Where was Gina Torres born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7615400552749634,
            "question": "What is Gina Torres' birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7604813575744629,
            "question": "What city is associated with Gina Torres' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7046873569488525,
            "question": "Can you tell me the location of Gina Torres' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4964754581451416,
            "question": "Gina Torres' origins can be traced back to which city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41138938069343567,
            "question": "In what state did Gina Torres come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17803160846233368,
            "question": "New York is known as the birthplace of...?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13647539913654327,
            "question": "Which famous actress hails from New York?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gina Torres was born in New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7061_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=New York is known as the birthplace of...?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7061_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what state did Gina Torres come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7061_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gina Torres' origins can be traced back to which city?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7061_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7061_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Gina Torres was born in Manhattan, New York, on April 25, 1969. Therefore, the statement \"Gina Torres was born in New York\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}